tracer here
Oh Youth truly is wasted on the young
at least statistically I've wasted less
than most
Kenji ready for some sparring practice
of course you are the only one I have
trouble keeping up with
what is it like to have that has to
change their past sometimes it doesn't
want to change
she is nice the Cavalry's here that's my
line
think I could have a look at one of
those bombs of yours over my dead body
lucio I'll race ya oh you're on
Hecuba then stay out of our way
hey tracer want to see who's faster race
you to the end of the match
turning up lucio haha yeah done and done
hey tracer you and Emily want to hit the
slope sometime absolutely if you think
you can keep up with us
on you born wearing all that yes but is
too late to change chaser you're so
amazing you inspire me may you're the
real hero
Tresa is it wrong for us to operate
outside the law that's a difficult
question Arisa I think there are times
when you just have to do what's right
you're so lucky tracer ever since I was
a little girl I dreamed of joining
overwatch maybe you'll still get your
chance who knows what the future holds
tracer have you thought about joining
helix we could always use a good pilot
Oh flattered really but I have some
other things occupying my time now
you need to slow down think about your
actions okay dad
sometimes I feel a little sick after
using my translocator I'm sure you know
what I mean tracer won't be a problem if
you just disappear forever
don't think I don't recognize that
device of yours I know you stole it
how can I say a girl just has to have
the latest tech
whoa it's me it's my chronal accelerator
malfunctioning again wait that's what I
was just thinking spooky
whoa it's me it's my chronal accelerator
malfunctioning again no I know how that
feels this is something else entirely
what you looking at an annoyance
Sancia it looks like we will be working
together don't think I'm happy about
that
oh so predictable even when you reverse
time you always make the same decisions
don't be so sure about that
Oh Winston got you favor for the last
time no more bananas
Winston you're an animal
empirical evidence suggests I'm a real
animal
need any adjustments to your chrono
accelerator I think just kidding Winston
it works great
Wow it's an honor to me a member of the
Shambhala one data was an inspiration to
me to us all
I miss him greatly
sorry cap
I know you can do better than that
Death Comes no one likes a thief
squished
that felt good
sorry big guy
it was Beauty killed the Beast
oh sorry Santa you could be my wingman
anytime
oh nice one Reinhardt's
Winston you're an animal
it will take more than that to keep
Genji out of the fight Winston